boozt.com 2012-05-27

# Boozt Fashion - Privacy Policy - Boozt.com UK

BZT Fashion AB and/or any of its subsidiaries or associated companies takes its relationship with all our users seriously, and this includes how we handle the data you give us. BZT Fashion AB is committed to meeting the requirements of all relevant laws and codes. This Privacy Policy sets out the ways BZT Fashion AB processes any personal data collected via its Website.

Our Website is free for you to browse through and read. We only ask for your email address for the following reasons;  
If you want to purchase product(s) from the Website.  
If you want to take part in a Prize Draw or Competition  
If you want to contact us, send us an email or offer feedback  
If you want to receive BZT Fashion AB news and exclusive offers via email  
We only collect personal information (such as your name and address details) if you choose to provide that information to us in response to our request.

We will require you to provide particular personal information such as your credit card details and your billing address for the purposes of completing your order. We will only use this information for the purposes of managing your order or your usage of the Website.  
Providing additional personal information is up to you. We collect personal information to enter you in Boozt.com and notify you of results, to e-mail you with updates, news and special offers, to respond to your questions or comments, to register you for certain features on the Website.

We will send you email updates unless you opt not to receive them.

We always provide you with the opportunity to opt in or out of receiving communication via email.  
BZT Fashion AB’s policy is to allow users to unsubscribe from our regular emails at any time. You can do this by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email you've received. Can you also Unsubscribe by clicking on the "-" sign under Newsletter Sign-up box - this will give you the option to Unsubscribe. Alternatively you can send an email to customer service.  
If you have sent a message asking us to stop sending emails, and this hasn’t happened, it may be because the email address to which we are sending them is not the same as the address you sent your request from. Please check the address we are using and include this information in your request. The easiest way to do this is to return to us the whole of the unwanted email. The address we are sending to is included at the bottom of the message.

BZT Fashion AB (and those people or companies employed by BZT Fashion AB who help make this Website, its content and its services) will process and use the information you tell us in order to respond to your feedback - like responding to problems, improving our services and gearing what we do to suit your requirements further.  
Beyond this, we will not share your information with any other company without your consent unless we are required to do so by law, if you have won a prize or if you have made a request for specific information. If you give us consent when you register with BZT Fashion AB, then we may share your information with other companies in order that they can contact you with information, promotions, products, services and offers that may be interesting to you  
We will never sell your information to any other company

BZT Fashion AB may use cookies in order to provide a better service or identify which pages on the Website are of special interest. A cookie is a small piece of information which a Website stores via your web browser on your PC and which can later be retrieved. Cookies cannot be read by a Website other than the one that set it. The main objective is to identify users and personalise their visit by customising web pages for them, for example by welcoming them by name next time they visit the same website. Most cookies last only through one session or visit to our Website. None will contain information that will enable anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or any other means. You can set up your web browser to inform you when cookies are set or to prevent cookies form being set.

We have instituted safeguards to check that our internal procedures meet our high policy standards. We also use our best efforts to be sure that third parties who work with us as our agents to make this Website and its contents available to you, and to fulfil your orders and requests, agree to protect personal information that they must access in order to serve our Website and our visitors. We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We offer links to other websites we use and recommend. However, we are not responsible for the content or information collection policies of websites operated by other companies. If you visit another website, we advise you to review their privacy and other policies.

Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted here.  
If BZT Fashion AB wishes to make material changes to the way we use your personal information we will ask for your consent before we do so.

Except as otherwise provided, BZT Fashion AB will NOT disclose any information processed by us to any third party, unless required to do so by law.  
© BZT Fashion AB 2011. All Rights Reserved.
